payleap.com 2012-12-27

# Payment Gateway and Online ePayments | PayLeap.com

**Effective date: 11/30/09**

This statement sets forth the privacy policy pertaining to this website, PayLeap.com (the “Site”). By using this site you expressly accept and agree to abide by the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy. This policy applies to “Personal Information” that we collect on-line. 

_PayLeap is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Web site www.payleap.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe._

_If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Customer support at 877.472.9532 or privacy@payleap.com. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at[http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url=www.payleap.com](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url=www.payleap.com)._

_TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns._

### Personally Identifying Information:

Personal Information means any information that personally identifies you, & may include your name, address, telephone number and email address. PayLeap will not share your Personal Information with other people except as discussed below. 

Besides Personal Information, when you access our website our servers may automatically collect information about your domain, internet browser, operating system, screen resolution, cookie preferences, and other data. None of this personally identifies you, and is collected only to measure usage patterns & trends concerning the website.

### External links:

For your convenience, our website may contain links to other sites. When you use a link to go from our site to another site this Privacy Policy is no longer in effect unless otherwise noted. PayLeap is not responsible for the privacy policies employed by web sites linked to or from our site nor for the information or content contained therein. 

We are committed to keeping your Personal Information secure and have taken all reasonable measures to protect this information from loss, misuse or alteration. However, we cannot be and are not responsible for unauthorized access to your Personal Information by hackers or others who have obtained such access through illegal measures.

### Secure Socket Layer:

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as social security number, national ID, personal health information) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, follow this link <http://www.comodo.com/e-commerce/ssl-certificates/ssl.php>. 

### Cookies:

This website may utilize “cookies” to enhance your visit to and navigation around the site. These cookies are also used to report anonymous statistical information concerning site usage that helps us improve the site. We do not use cookies to identify or track any Personal Information. You can alter your internet browser settings to prevent accepting any cookies if you so desire. Rejecting a cookie may affect the browsing and navigation of our site and you may be required to re-enter certain information when browsing and/or returning to the site. 

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. This site uses Google Analytics to track the user data. For further information about how Google uses cookies, please visit <http://code.google.com/apis/analytics/docs/concepts/gaConceptsCookies.html#HowGAUsesCookies>. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

### Third Party Cookies

The use of cookies by our [partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers] is covered by our privacy statement. We do have access or control over these cookies. Our [partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers] use session ID cookies [to make it easier for you to navigate our site, in order for you to use the site, etc.] 

### Exceptions:

It is our policy to maintain all Personal Information as confidential except as may be necessary to fulfill a function or purpose such as, but not limited to, those listed below: 

  * For the specific purpose for which it was submitted (informational inquiry, to receive product information, testimonials, contest entries, request for proposal, etc.) 
  * To improve the content, appearance and utility of the site
  * To accumulate usage patterns and trends for internal research
  * To notify visitors regarding updates to the site 

### Presiding law:

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

We may also disclose Personal Information about you that is in our possession upon governmental request or if required to do so by law or based on our good faith belief that it is necessary to protect our site and the users of our site.

We may contract with other companies to provide certain services, including, but not limited to, e-mail distribution, market research and promotions management, including promotional email.

We may provide these companies only with the information needed to perform their services (which may include Personal Information) and work closely with them to maintain the confidentiality of your Personal Information as described in this privacy policy. These companies are prohibited from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone else. However, we cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Information with these companies and are not liable for misuse of it by others.

We do not share, sell, rent or trade personal identifying information with third parties for their promotional purposes. In the event PayLeap buys or sells assets, subsidiaries, or business units, your Personal Information may be transferred as an asset. Generally, such transferred Personal Information remains subject to the promises made in the applicable pre-existing Privacy Policy Statement.

You may obtain a summary of your Personal Information on record with us by submitting an e-mail to [privacy@payleap.com](mailto:privacy@payleap.com) or by writing to PayLeap, 3594 E US Hwy 30, Warsaw, IN, 46580 or by phoning **1-877-472-9532 (877.4PAYLEAP)**. When contacting us be sure to provide your exact e-mail address, name, postal address, and/or telephone number in order to be sure we handle your request correctly. You may request that (1) we correct or update any of your Personal Information, (2) your Personal Information not be provided to third parties except for order fulfillment, or (3) that your Personal Information be removed from our active marketing databases.

### Customer Testimonials/Comments/Reviews:

We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. 

### Reserved right to change/modify:

As we continue to develop this site we reserve the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy. This policy was last updated on October 1, 2009. You should check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of this site following the posting of changes implies acceptance of those changes. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

### Disclaimer:

Do not provide your Personal Information to anyone unless you are certain of that party’s identity. PayLeap does not request Personal Information via e-mail. If you suspect someone is trying to obtain your Personal Information by impersonating PayLeap, please contact us by sending an e-mail to [privacy@payleap.com](mailto:privacy@payleap.com) or by phoning **877.472.9532 (877.4PAYLEAP)**. 

### Contacts:

When you enter in 3rd party PII (name, email address, phone number and address) We offer this feature for to create and deliver to you emails such as our newsletters, surveys or other email messages containing product and event information, or promotions. PayLeap may also use this information to send letters, promotions and other correspondence via the mail. 

You may contact us at [info@payleap.com](mailto:info@payleap.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.
